<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ReactomePA</title>
    <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/ReactomePA/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ReactomePA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the Artistic-2.0 license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 12:08:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://guangchuangyu.github.io/ReactomePA/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ReactomePA: Reactome Pathway Analysis</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/ReactomePA/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 12:08:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/ReactomePA/</guid>
      <description>This package provides functions for pathway analysis based on REACTOME pathway database. It implements enrichment analysis, gene set enrichment analysis and several functions for visualization.
ReactomePA is released within the Bioconductor project and the source code is hosted in  GitHub.
 Author Guangchuang Yu, School of Public Health, The University of Hong Kong.
     
  Citation Please cite the following article when using ReactomePA:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/ReactomePA/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/ReactomePA/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Vignettes  https://bioconductor.org/packages/devel/bioc/vignettes/ReactomePA/inst/doc/ReactomePA.html    Blog posts  News and updates  ReactomePA: an R/Bioconductor package for reactome pathway analysis and visualization BioC 3.1: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.2: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.3: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.4: NEWS of my BioC packages    Enrichment analysis  functional enrichment for GTEx paper functional enrichment analysis with NGS data leading edge analysis why clusterProfiler fails Comparison of clusterProfiler and GSEA-P    Visualization  dotplot for enrichment result dotplot for GSEA result enrichment map showCategory parameter for visualizing compareCluster output   Find out more on https://guangchuangyu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featured Articles</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/ReactomePA/featured-articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/ReactomePA/featured-articles/</guid>
      <description>Let us know if you have published using ReactomePA and your publication will be featured here.
2016 Evolution of multiple cell clones over a 29-year period of a CLL patient. Nature Communications. 2016, 7:13765.
Increased DNA methylation variability in type 1 diabetes across three immune effector cell types. Nature Communications. 2016, 7:13555.
Transcriptional Dynamics During Human Adipogenesis and its Link to Adipose Morphology and Distribution. Diabetes. 2016.
Lineage-Specific Genome Architecture Links Enhancers and Non-coding Disease Variants to Target Gene Promoters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>